{
    "id": "ebf6f4ad81d841f4b97b093c5bdb1ffe",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was late because my car ……………… on the way to work.",
            "description": "When something breaks down, it stops functioning.",
            "answers": [
                "broke up",
                "broke down",
                "broke off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. with her best friend when he lied to her.",
            "description": "To break up with somebody is to end your relationship with them.",
            "answers": [
                "broke up",
                "broke off",
                "broke down"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ………………………. when she heard that she had failed.",
            "description": "To break down is to lose control of your emotions.",
            "answers": [
                "broke off",
                "broke down",
                "broke out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The warden …………………….. our conversation.",
            "description": "To break in on is to interrupt.",
            "answers": [
                "broke in on",
                "broke up on",
                "broke out on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Cholera …………………… after the floods.",
            "description": "When a disease breaks out, it appears and spreads suddenly.",
            "answers": [
                "broke up",
                "broke out",
                "broke off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A dangerous prisoner ………………………. the high security prison yesterday.",
            "description": "To break out of jail is to escape from captivity.",
            "answers": [
                "broke out of",
                "broke up of",
                "broke off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Please …………………….. your coat. It is very cold.",
            "description": "To put on coat is to wear it.",
            "answers": [
                "put on",
                "put off",
                "try on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind if I ……………………. TV? I would like to watch the match.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turned up",
                "turned on",
                "turned in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Excuse me. Where can I …………………….. the shirt?",
            "description": "To try on a shirt is to try wearing it to see if it fits you.",
            "answers": [
                "try in",
                "try out",
                "try on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you don’t …………………….. the train now, it will leave without you.",
            "description": "To get on the train is to board it.",
            "answers": [
                "get in",
                "get on",
                "get up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I ……………………… working now?",
            "description": "To carry on something is to continue doing it.",
            "answers": [
                "carry out",
                "carry on",
                "carry in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must …………………….. smoking.",
            "description": "To give up smoking is to quit it.",
            "answers": [
                "give up",
                "give in",
                "give out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}